<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Tomoya Shimura</title>
    <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Tomoya Shimura</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language>
    <atom:link href="https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3. その他</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conference proceedings or abstracts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T. and N.Mori (2017) Future Change of Storm Surge Risk under Global Warming Based on Mega-ensemble Global Climate Projections (d4PDF), Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 11p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;N.Mori, T. Shimura, H. Kamahori and A. Chawla (2017) Historical Wave Climate Hindcasts Based on JRA-55, Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 8p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2014) Future Projection of Ocean Wave Climate Change Using Multi-SST Ensemble Experiments, Proceedings of the 34rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2014), No.34, 12p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2013) Future Projections of Global Wave Climate by Multi-SST and Multi-Physics Ensemble Experiments, Proceedings of 13th International Workshop on Wave Hindcasting and Forecasting, 9p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mori, N., T. Shimura, S. Nakajo, D. Tsujio, T. Yasuda, H. Mase and K.D. Suh (2013) Projection of future wave climate change and application to coastal structure design, Proceedings of Breakwater Conference, Edinburgh, 9p&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2012) Wave Dynamics and Its Impact to Wave Climate Projection, Proceedings of the 33rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2012), No.33, 11p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mori, N., T. Shimura, S. Nakajo, T. Yasuda, and H. Mase (2012). Multi-model ensemble projection of future coastal climate change, Proceedings of the 33rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2012), No.33, 11p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T., N. Mori, S. Nakajo, T. Yasuda and H. Mase (2011) Extreme Wave Climate Change Projection at the End of 21st Century, Proceedings of Asia Pacific Coasts 2011 (APAC2011), No.39, 8p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mori, N., T., Shimura, T. Yasuda and H. Mase (2010) Dynamic Projection of Future Wave Climate Change in Global Scale, The WCRP/JCOMM Workshop on Coordinated Ocean Wave Climate Projections (COWCLIP), World Meteorological Organization, Geneva, 1p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shimura, T., N. Mori, T. Yasuda and H. Mase (2010) Wave Climate Change Projection at the End of 21st Century, The 32nd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE2010), No.32, 2p.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oral/Poster Presentations:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. 論文(和文誌)</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2208/journalofjsce.25-17141&#34;&gt;Yao, T., N. Mori, T. Shimura, T. Miyashita (2025) TROPICAL CYCLONE CHARACTERISTICS FROM PRE-INDUSTRIAL TO DIFFERENT GLOBAL WARMING LEVELS BASED ON D4PDF DATASET, ，土木学会論文集, 2025, 81巻17号, 25-17141&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;ttps://doi.org/10.2208/jscejj.25-17255&#34;&gt;行貝高虎・森 信人・志村 智也・宮下 卓也 (2025) 大規模アンサンブル気候データd4PDFを学習に用いたCNN-LSTMによる台風経路予測，土木学会論文集, 2025, 81巻17号, 25-17255&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2208/jscejj.25-17216&#34;&gt;山本悠・志村智也・森信人・宮下卓也 (2025) F-net 常時微動観測における二次脈動から台風高波の統計的推定，土木学会論文集, 2025, 81巻17号, 25-17216&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2208/jscejj.25-17196&#34;&gt;西野 藍・宮下 卓也・安田 誠宏・志村 智也・森 信人 (2025) メソ気象予報モデルデータ解析と数値実験による九州西岸における気象津波発生要因の解明, 土木学会論文集, 2025, 81巻17号, 25-17196&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2208/jscejj.24-17026&#34;&gt;山崎豪太・志村智也・森信人・宮下卓也 (2024) 漂流ブイ観測周波数スペクトルのデータ同化による台風高波推算, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17026&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.2208/jscejj.24-17044&#34;&gt;山本詩恩・宮下卓也・安田誠宏・志村 智也・森信人 (2024) 気候変動シナリオの違いによる三大湾ゼロメートル地帯の浸水危険度変化分析, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17044&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1. Journal papers</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1029/2024JC021929&#34;&gt;Shimura, T., Y. Masumi, N. Mori, T. Miyashita (2025) The 20-year highest tropical cyclone‐generated waves associated with the maximum energy of seismic noises, Journal of Geophysical Research-Oceans, 130, e2024JC021929&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1080/21664250.2025.2574778&#34;&gt;Sato, S., N. Mori, T. Shimura, T. Miyashita (2025) Modeling wind wave growth based on phase-resolving wave model, Coastal Engineering Journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1080/21664250.2025.2564587&#34;&gt;Molteni-Pérez F., T. Miyashita, T. Shimura, N. Mori  (2025) Analysis of historical extreme coastal water level and its contributors along the South American Pacific coast, Coastal Engineering Journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
