<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Tomoya Shimura</title>
    <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Tomoya Shimura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language><atom:link href="https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3. その他</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</guid>
      <description>Conference proceedings or abstracts:
 Shimura, T. and N.Mori (2017) Future Change of Storm Surge Risk under Global Warming Based on Mega-ensemble Global Climate Projections (d4PDF), Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 11p. N.Mori, T. Shimura, H. Kamahori and A. Chawla (2017) Historical Wave Climate Hindcasts Based on JRA-55, Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 8p. Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2014) Future Projection of Ocean Wave Climate Change Using Multi-SST Ensemble Experiments, Proceedings of the 34rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2014), No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. 論文(和文誌)</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</guid>
      <description>山崎豪太・志村智也・森信人・宮下卓也 (2024) 漂流ブイ観測周波数スペクトルのデータ同化による台風高波推算, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17026
  山本詩恩・宮下卓也・安田誠宏・志村 智也・森信人 (2024) 気候変動シナリオの違いによる三大湾ゼロメートル地帯の浸水危険度変化分析, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17044
  澁谷容子・森信人・志村智也 (2024) JRA-55waveを用いた確率波高算出の可能性について, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号,24-17019
  岡田智晴・森信人・志村智也 (2024) 1.5度上昇シナリオのd4PDFデータを用いた台風のトラッキングと温暖化レベルに基づいた台風への影響評価, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17048
  長谷川裕亮・志村智也・宮下卓也・Yu-Lin Tsai・馬場 繁幸・森信人 (2024) マングローブ樹形を考慮した波浪変形モデルの開発, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17004
  Sandi, C., N. Mori, T. Shimura, T. Miyashita (2024) Relation of sea level anomaly and teleconnection pattern in southeast asia, 土木学会論文集, 2024, 80巻17号, 24-17268</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Journal papers</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</guid>
      <description>2025
  Shimura, T., Y. Masumi, N. Mori, T. Miyashita (2025) The 20-year highest tropical cyclone‐generated waves associated with the maximum energy of seismic noises, Journal of Geophysical Research-Oceans, 130, e2024JC021929
  Miyashita, T., A. Nishino, S. Watanabe, T. Yasuda, N. Mori, T. Shimura, T.-C. Ho (2025) Contribution of microtopography off the Ryukyu Islands to coastal sea-level amplification during the 2022 Tonga meteotsunami, Earth, Planets and Space, 77, 20</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
