<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Tomoya Shimura</title>
    <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Tomoya Shimura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>-その他</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</guid>
      <description>Conference proceedings or abstracts:
 Shimura, T. and N.Mori (2017) Future Change of Storm Surge Risk under Global Warming Based on Mega-ensemble Global Climate Projections (d4PDF), Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 11p. N.Mori, T. Shimura, H. Kamahori and A. Chawla (2017) Historical Wave Climate Hindcasts Based on JRA-55, Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 8p. Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2014) Future Projection of Ocean Wave Climate Change Using Multi-SST Ensemble Experiments, Proceedings of the 34rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2014), No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>-論文(和文誌)</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</guid>
      <description>桑江 朝比呂・三戸 勇吾・有川 太郎・石川 洋一・木所 英昭・澁谷 容子・志村 智也・清野 聡子・羽角 華奈子・茂木 博匡・山北 剛久・李 漢洙・金 洙列・久保田 真一・倉原 義之介・辻尾 大樹・二宮 順一・伴野 雅之・古市 尚基・安田 誠宏・森 信人・武若 聡（2020）今後の我が国の沿岸分野における気候変動対応で取り組むべき課題に関する意向調査，土木学会論文集(海岸工学), Vol.77, pp.1-17. 森 信人・福井 信気・志村 智也 (2020) 気候変動を考慮した我が国の三大湾の高潮最大潮位偏差についての研究レビュー, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学), Vol.76, pp.1-6. 志村 智也・森 信人・浦野 大介・水田 亮 (2020) 波浪結合全球大気気候モデルによる波向－風向のずれを考慮した海面抵抗係数の台風統計量への系統的影響評価, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学), Vol.76, pp. I_151-I_156. 浦野 大介・森 信人・志村 智也・水田 亮 (2020) 海洋表層混合を考慮した全球大気・波浪・海洋結合モデルによる台風強度特性の評価, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学), Vol. 76, pp. I_1117-I_1122. 宮内 海峰・森 信人・志村 智也・建部 洋晶 (2020) 気候変動に伴う日本周辺海域を対象とした海面上昇量の予測不確実性, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学), Vol. 76, pp.I_1135-I_1140. 横山 彼杜・安田 誠宏・金 洙列・中條 壮大・志村 智也 (2020) 確率台風モデルを援用した瀬戸内海における高潮の統計的予測手法に関する研究, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学), Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal papers</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</guid>
      <description>Morim, J., S. Vitousek, M. Hemer, B. Reguero, L. Erikson, M. Casas-Prat, X.L. Wang, A. Semedo, N. Mori, T. Shimura, L. Mentaschi, B. Timmermans (2021) Global-scale changes to extreme ocean wave events due to anthropogenic warming, Environmental Research Letters, 16, 074056.
  Odériz I., R. Silva, T.R. Mortlock, N. Mori, T. Shimura, A. Webb, R. Padilla-Hernandez, S. Villers (2021) Natural Variability and Warming Signals in Global Ocean Wave Climates, Geophysical Research Letters, 48, e2021GL093622.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>