<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Tomoya Shimura</title>
    <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Tomoya Shimura</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-JP</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3. その他</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/03_etc/</guid>
      <description>Conference proceedings or abstracts:
 Shimura, T. and N.Mori (2017) Future Change of Storm Surge Risk under Global Warming Based on Mega-ensemble Global Climate Projections (d4PDF), Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 11p. N.Mori, T. Shimura, H. Kamahori and A. Chawla (2017) Historical Wave Climate Hindcasts Based on JRA-55, Proceedings of Coastal Dynamics 2017, 8p. Shimura, T., N.Mori, T.Yasuda and H.Mase (2014) Future Projection of Ocean Wave Climate Change Using Multi-SST Ensemble Experiments, Proceedings of the 34rd International Conference on Coastal Engineering (ICCE 2014), No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. 論文(和文誌)</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/02_journal_jp/</guid>
      <description>志村智也・William J. PRINGLE・森信人・宮下卓也・吉田康平 (2021) 過去から温暖化条件下の将来へのシームレスな全球高潮・高波評価, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp. I_949─I_954.
  岡田 智晴・志村 智也・Adrean WEBB・宮下 卓也・森 信人・水田 亮 (2021) CMIP6 実験にもとづくスラブ海洋結合全球大気気候モデルを用いた気候変動の台風への影響評価, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp. I_961─I_966.
  髙木 雅史・森 信人・二宮 順一・志村 智也・宮下 卓也 (2021) 風波砕波による海洋表層混合の台風への影響, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp. I_997─I_1002.
  宮内 海峰・森 信人・志村 智也・建部 洋晶 (2021) 全球気候モデルMIROC6を用いた東アジア海域における海面水位の自然変動成分の評価, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp. I_967─I_972.
  小池 宏之進・森 信人・志村 智也・宮下 卓也・二宮 順一 (2021) MRI-AGCM150年予測を用いた気候変動に伴う爆弾低気圧の将来変化と日本沿岸波浪への影響, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp. I_955─I_960.
  Audrius SABŪNAS, Nobuhito MORI, Nobuki FUKUI, Tomoya SHIMURA, Takuya MIYASHITA, Adrean WEBB (2021) Assessing Social Impact of Storm Surge and Sea Level Rise Compound Effects in Viti Levu, Fiji, Comparing With The Historical TC Records, 土木学会論文集B2(海岸工学)，77巻2号, pp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Journal papers</title>
      <link>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tomoyashimura.github.io/publications/01_journal/</guid>
      <description>2022
  Shimura, T., W.J. Pringle, N. Mori, T. Miyashita, K. Yoshida (2022) Seamless Projections of Global Storm Surge and Ocean Waves under a Warming Climate, Geophysical Research Letters, 49, e2021GL097427
  Shimura, T., N. Mori, D. Urano, T. Takemi, R. Mizuta (2022) Tropical Cyclone Characteristics Represented by the Ocean Wave Coupled Atmospheric Global Climate Model Incorporating Wave-Dependent Momentum Flux, Journal of Climate, 35, 499–515.
  Fukui, N.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>